A Guide to the Wakefield High School Posters, 1968-1970
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
Wakefield High School Posters, 1968-1970
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
RG 188
1 box.
Wakefield High School
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Wakefield alumna David Crist in 2006.
Scope and Content
RG 188, Wakefield High School Posters Collection, is approximately 90 posters created by students at Wakefield High School. These posters, made on school premises using school supplies, advertised school events, clubs, and activities circa 1970. Many of the events have a month and day listed on the poster and some reference local bands scheduled to appear. In keeping with the times and the creators, there were also several abstract drawings or interpretations of well-known people and sayings. There is one poster for a student election that has candidate photographs taped to the poster.
Arrangement
All posters are silkscreen images on poster paper of various sizes. They are all housed in one oversized box. Every poster has been digitized and is easily accessible online with individual descriptions of each poster. Titles listed here in quotes ("") are taken from the poster's text; some entire titles and partial titles are supplied by the processor.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
For more information about the county's schools, see RG 7, Arlington Public Schools. More Wakefield-related material can be found in RG 167, Wakefield Alumni Association Records.
Digitized posters can be found here.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Posters.; Wakefield High School (Arlington, Va.); Arlington (Va.); Arlington County (Va.)
Contents List
- BOX 1
  - "Stop the War, Buy! US Savings Bonds"
  - "PSI Snow Queen Ball," 1970
  - "Senior Class Picnick," 1969
  - "Join Wakefield's First Service Club, PSI," 1970
  - "Wakefield Day, May 9"
  - "Buy a Pendulum"
  - "Another Stupid Dance"
  - "Pappagallo's and Keyettes Fashion Show"
  - Queen of Spades
  - "Car Rally"
  - "Dance, May 10, Featuring Blue Penny and Sweet Wine"
  - "Junior Prom in the Age of Aquarius"
  - "Pollution Evening Meeting," 1970
  - "Wakefield's Spring Art Show and Creative Arts Night"
  - "County-Wide Dance"
  - Jim Morrison
  - "Celebrate Life Baccalaureate Folk Service," 1970
  - "Junior Prom"
  - "Bob Jones Senior Class Treasurer"
  - "Wakefield Day Moonlight Dance"
  - "Wakefield Art Show"
  - "Vote Kay Kjellstrom for Jr. Class Secretary," 1969
  - "Cut Out Checkers Board"
  - "After Game Dance," 1970
  - "Swim Party"
  - "Hop Hop Hop To It, Seniors! Dues Drive"
  - "Varsity Tomfoolery," 1970
  - "Crafts Fair"
  - "Revitalize the Youth Council"
  - "Science Honor Society Presents Michael Ryan on Gravity Waves"
  - "Sweetheart Ball"
  - "Wanted Dead or Alive: Cecil Formossa's Mafia Spaghetti Going Away Party"
  - "Write for the Pendulum"
  - "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof" Movie Showing
  - "Jr.-Sr. Basketball Game," 1970
  - "Crafts Fair"
  - "A Dance Featuring The Shades," 1969
  - "Keyettes Sell Mistletoe Corsages"
  - "Would You Rather Switch Than Walk?"
  - "See 'Dracula' By the Film Club"
  - "Jr.s Inve$t in Yourself!"
  - "American Educational Week," 1969
  - "Drill Team Says Buy Pom Poms"
  - "Take a Deep Breath," Earth Day, 1970
  - "Vote for Sally Oaks"
  - "Here Come the Warriors," 1969
  - "Come See Winter Track"
  - "Miss Wakefield Contest"
  - "Cecil Formosa's Going Away Party"
  - "The Art Department Presents the Slolyniskaneder Film Festival!"
  - "David & Lisa," Fall Play, 1969
  - "Dark of the Moon," Fall Play, 1968
  - "Kappa Open House"
  - "West Side Story," Spring Play, 1970
  - "Buy the Pendulum"
  - "Car Rally"
  - "Finian's Rainbow," Spring Play, 1969
  - "Daffodil Day"
  - "Joy Baby Jr. Week"
  - "Smile! It's Jr. Week"
  - "Smoking Courts," 1969
  - "Senior Auction"
  - "Films! 20 Snazzaroo Movies"
  - "Senior '70 Week", 1970
  - "Jim Schillinger SCA President, Wayne Parks, SCA Vice-President"
  - "Fashion Show - 'Night Before Christmas'"
  - "Spring Concert"
  - "Art Department Presents Popcorn For Sale"
  - "Spring Concerts"
  - "Enchanted Reign Forest Featuring The Magic Reign"
  - "Who Will Be Delta's Mr. Irresistible?"
  - "Area High School Film Festival"
  - "Vote Ed Choate for President and Danny Grahm for Vice President"
  - "The Anything Box"
  - "Cold Duck"
  - "Open Public Discussion on Drugs with Dr. Kenneth Haggarty and Members of the Arlington County Board," 1969
  - "Omicron Secret Easter Bunny"
  - "Creative Arts Night"
  - "Buy a Daffodil From a Keyette"
  - "Seniors - Games in the Senior Court"
  - "Wakefield Gymnastics"
  - "Beatles"
  - "Drug Lecture Series at Wakefield"
  - "Go to Anthony and the Imperials"
  - "2nd Annual Crafts Fair"
  - "The Magic Reign"
  - "PHI and SAN Present the Enchanted Reign Forest," 1969